vocm.com 2019-09-04

# Radio - Privacy Policy | Stingray

This privacy policy applies to the use of all Newfoundland Capital Corporation and Newcap Radio (collectively “Newcap”) websites.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using Newcap websites.

**Personal Information**

“Personal Information” in this policy is defined as information that could reasonably personally identify you as an individual. Examples would include your name, mailing and e-mail addresses, age, birthday, telephone number, picture and voice recording. This policy describes the types of Personal Information that we collect, how we collect it, why we collect it and what we use it for.

“Non-identifiable Personal Information” is information that by itself cannot be associated with you as an identifiable individual, such as browser type, information about your operating system, device, and the unique identifier assigned to your device.

“Browsing Data” is information that Newcap and its third party partners may collect about your web browsing and app usage, such as the date and time you visited certain websites or apps, pages of such websites or apps that you visited, the names or types of mobile app that you visited, and other data such as page visits, ads shown, ads clicked and conversions.

It is our policy not to associate Non-identifiable Personal Information or Browsing Data with customers, even though we verify some kinds of technical information to ensure that our websites are optimized to serve our customers.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Registration is not required in order to use or access Newcap websites. We may collect Personal Information when you enter a contest or other promotional activities through our websites, when you participate in interactive online activities and/or when you contact us to make requests or comment on our services. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to enter a contest or promotional activity or leave comments or provide articles.

If you register, and in the process provide us with Personal Information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

Particular care is employed when we collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Personal Information from children is not required to obtain access to, surf or view the content of our websites. However, for a child to participate in our contests or promotions, certain Personal Information may be required. Under this scenario, we may collect the first and last name (or user name) of the child, the child’s e-mail address, home address, birth date and gender, as well as the name, home address, e-mail address and telephone number of the child’s parent or guardian.

Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 is only collected when it is necessary for the purposes of verifying the child’s age, administering the child’s participation in the contest or promotion and, if the child wins a prize, contacting the child’s parent or guardian. We will not use, maintain or disclose this Personal Information for any other purpose, without consent.

The child’s parent or guardian can contact us at any time to get more information about our Personal Information practices or to remove the child’s Personal Information from our records.

We also provide visitors to our websites the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we may ask the visitor for his or her email address, first name and last name, or username, address, city, province, phone number, postal code and birth date. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by emailing us at privacy@newcap.ca, by replying to any email we send you and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line, or by visiting one of our websites and logging into your account and choosing unsubscribe.

Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third party organization except in accordance with this Policy or with your express consent. Effective July 13, 2018, we will, however, include your email address in our email list to create what is referred to as a “Lookalike” audience. A “Lookalike” audience on social media allows Newcap to reach out to more people who resemble Newcap’s established client base. A lookalike audience uses either an existing custom audience or conversion data (conversion pixels) as a “seed” and an audience is built of similar users. Lookalike audiences can be used to support certain Newcap business objectives, such as increasing listenership to Newcap’s radio stations or providing additional marketing exposure to our advertising partners. If you do not want your email address used for this purpose, you may request your email address be removed from our email list by emailing us at privacy@newcap.ca, by replying to any email we send you and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line, or by visiting one of our websites and logging into your account and choosing to unsubscribe from any email communication.  If you advise us that you do not want your email address to be used for this purpose after July 13, 2018, we will not use your email address for this purpose on a go-forward basis.

**Third-Party Advertising**

Newcap has engaged Acuity Ads as its advertising agent to serve ads from third parties when you visit Newcap websites. Acuity Ads privacy policy is available at the following link: https://www.acuityads.com/privacy-policy/.  These advertisers may use Browsing Data compiled by us or them about your visits to Newcap and other websites and your response to ads in order to provide advertisements on websites that they serve about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We do not target children under the age of 13.

Except as otherwise detailed in this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information will not be shared with third parties. Any third-party promotions and offers will only be made available through us on behalf of the third parties.

**Log Files and Cookies**

Newcap may collect Non-identifiable Personal Information through the use of cookies, web beacons, or similar files (collectively “cookies”). We use this information to assess general usage patterns, including identifying repeat users, collect demographic information, administer and make improvements to Newcap websites to tailor our visitors’ experiences and display content according to their preferences so as to make it more useful to you and other users. Newcap, our affiliate companies and such other third party as we may designate reserve the right to use, maintain, update, disclose and/or sell Non-identifiable Personal Information to third parties.

Newcap may, from time to time, provide Browsing Data (such as the number of times you have viewed an ad to serve additional ads about goods and services that may be of interest to you) to third party advertising companies.  Using the Browsing Data collected, Newcap and third parties can infer such things as browser type, operating system, browser language, internet protocol address, internet service provider, and mobile advertising identifier for mobile devices.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any Personal Information you have submitted while on our site.

We use both session ID Cookies and persistent Cookies. A session Cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session Cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent Cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

Most browser software allows you to delete cookies. You should consult your browser instructions or help screen for information on how to delete cookies. This may interfere with our ability to personalize your experience at our websites and be recognized, or may slow down performance.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any third party advertisers on our websites.

The following link has useful information about how to opt out of cookies that are placed by companies who are members of the network NAI (Network Advertising Initiative): NAI Opt-out.  For more information on online behavioural advertising or to opt-out from other third-party advertising companies, visit the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada website at Your Ad Choices.

**Access to Personal Information**

If your Personal Information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at privacy@newcap.ca. You may also complete any corrections, updates or deletion requests by visiting a websites login area; you also may make your request by phone or postal mail at the address/phone number indicated at the end of this privacy policy.

**Location & Security**

We use servers located at facilities in the United States to host our websites and store information and data (including Personal Information). Newcap follows accepted industry standards to protect any Personal Information you have provided to us, including by employing feasible physical, technological, electronic and organizational safeguards. Examples of safeguards include: limited access to relevant information by authorized employees only, allowing safeguard through passwords or personal identification numbers (PINs) to your account, and use of firewalls and encryption technology for certain electronically stored information. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore – as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at privacy@newcap.ca.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our websites may contain links to other websites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our websites.

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or postal mail, our contact information is as follows:

privacy@stingray.com  
730, rue Wellington, Montréal (Québec) Canada H3C 1T4  
514-664-1244

This privacy policy was last updated in October, 2018.
